<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[fablifestyle]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[fablifestyle]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 13:32:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Fab Lifestyle]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A Fab Lifestyle</h1><p>A Fab Lifestyle is what we all crave for, no matter what amount of money is attached to the perception. With this site I would like to take you along the journey of life, how the choices we make impact our lives and how, in that respect, we are the masters of our own destiny. Happiness can be found in the tiniest little thing. The singing of a bird, sitting in front of your tent while camping. Reading a book that takes you to great adventures, preparing the best food, or maybe just some French fries... Or maybe your fab lifestyle wants that luxury yacht, villa, car, exotic traveling, or simply a life without bothering about finances. Whether you have a profession or are an entrepreneur, there are moments galore that you wonder: is this what I really want? Is this the thing that I daily wish to work on? Why do we all work from 9 to 5? Why are we all in the rat race? Never forget that we own our individual creative minds. There is a difference in things we should all adhere to, but our creativity makes life worthwhile, exciting and makes things grow. Just saying: there are more ways that lead to Rome :-)Finding my way through life brought me to places on internet where there is so much to learn from people in all kinds of fields. Personal development is one of them, spiritual awareness, and making money online are niches that are extensively being promoted. It can be a long way to find what exactly what ingredients you want that will suit your needs in order to create that fab lifestyle for you. The most important thing is that there are so many ways to create your personal fab lifestyle... join me on the journey.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9e530407226c50b50f1b9ebf7a07a5d98de4500c.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>undefineda-fab-lifestyle/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">89794d75-3d2e-4308-a632-d2155f98e2ab</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 13:31:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>